Zsombor Czaban

Krööpilänkatu 4C 42B, Turku, 60210

+36 30 814 7614 zsombor130@gmail.com



Work experience

Taboola / Algorithm engineer intern

Sept 2023 - Jan 2024, Budapest

Jun 2022 - Sept 2023, Budapest

meantime.

At taboola, I worked on their e-commerce recommendation system and I helped to develop in-house solutions to various problems. I got used to the Big Tech company environment and learned a lot in the

BitKnights / junior servicenow developer

During my time at BitKnights I was working on several projects. Including ITSM implementations, merges and maintenances.

I learned the fundamentals of agile software development, and also improved my teamwork skills.

I also got hands-on experience about how complicated big systems can get, and why clean and simple code/infrastructure is important.

Dr.Code / teacher

May 2018 - 2019, Kecskemét

While I was in highschool, I teached kids in primary school how to program in Scratch. (Scratch is a simple and intuitive programming language)

Working as a teacher taught me how important communication is.

Education

Åbo Akademi

Jan 2024 - Present, Turku

I'm an exchange student at Åbo Akademi. I take computer science courses from both Åbo Akademi and The University of Turku.

Eötvös Loránd Tudományegyetem

Sept 2021 - Present, Budapest

I study computer science at ELTE in Hungary.

I only have my thesis left to write after my exchange to get my Bsc.

Skills

I have worked with: Java, Python, Javascript, Typescript, Vue, Kubernetes, Jenkins, ClickHouse, Sql, MySql, ServiceNow, Jira

I'm also great with: C++, C#, Php, React, Laravel, Haskel, Flutter

I'm fluent in english (I have a C1 language exam certificate) And I'm getting better in Finnish day by day!

About me

I'm an Hungarian exchange student living in Finland. I love the Finnish culture, and the mentality of the Finnish people. I'm planning to move here, or at least do my masters at a Finnish university.

I'm always eager to learn. I'm really passionate about the field of Al, and I love algorithms.

I try to broaden my horizons as much as I can, so I can have a solid foundation to start my career off from.

Highschool awards

In 2017 I won a national math competition in Hungary. Since 2018 I've been a leader at 121. Dr. Vetéssy Géza scout troop.

In 2021, I won 4th place with 2 special prizes for my team in the "Ötletből jövő" competition. (It's an idea competition where teams of 1-5 people have to come up with an idea and plan a business around it on a theoretical level)